Baruch, Ismar Compilation of U.S. Employment Service and U.S. Civil Service Documents 6099
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Ismar Baruch Compilation of U.S. Employment Service and U.S. Civil Service Documents
1789-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Baruch, Ismar
U.S. Employment Service
U.S. Civil Service
6099
47 cubic feet
47 linear ft.
Publications.
"This collection of documents, pamphlets, and manuscripts was willed to the U.S. Civil Service Commission Library by Ismar Baruch on his death in 1956. Since Mr. Baruch numbered among his hobbies both bookbinding and photography, along with whittling and philately, he bound the collection himself and photographed his own bookplate. The collection relates predominately to the Federal civil service, but includes a few general compilations on public personnel administration and classification. Most of the material is arranged chronologically, but, with classification and pay in separate sections since theses are the two major areas covered. The selection of documents and papers made by Mr. Baruch for retention and binding reflects his wide range of activity and research in classification and pay areas and presents an excellent historical picture of legislative and executive activities, particularly during the period 1914-1954." - p. iii of Mr. Baruch's guide
7053757
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 25, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 28, 2015
Scope and Contents
"This collection of documents, pamphlets, and manuscripts was willed to the U.S. Civil Service Commission Library by Ismar Baruch on his death in 1956. Since Mr. Baruch numbered among his hobbies both bookbinding and photography, along with whittling and philately, he bound the collection himself and photographed his own bookplate. The collection relates predominately to the Federal civil service, but includes a few general compilations on public personnel administration and classification. Most of the material is arranged chronologically, but, with classification and pay in separate sections since theses are the two major areas covered. The selection of documents and papers made by Mr. Baruch for retention and binding reflects his wide range of activity and research in classification and pay areas and presents an excellent historical picture of legislative and executive activities, particularly during the period 1914-1954." - p. iii of Mr. Baruch's guide
"Since Mr. Baruch was an attorney the collection also includes a number of volumes of internal law memoranda, decisions, compilations, and cases. He was well known as a lecturer in personnel administration at local universities and some of his printed lectures and notes are included. He was chairman of the committee of the Civil Service Assembly which prepared the classic text on position classification and was in the process of developing a similar text on pay administration. The preliminary notes and working papers for this book are in the collection. The bibliography of his papers, publications and articles indicates the prolific writings of a scholarly gentleman interested in all phases of Federal personnel administration, both currently and historically. A particularly personal item well remembered by his many friends in Federal personnel circles is a collection of doodles sketched at various conferences. The spine title has usually been used to identify individual volumes or collections, but since there is considerable overlap in dates the earliest date has been used in the listing. The material is arranged on the shelves according to the order shown in this compilation and has no other identification than the spine title. Some sets of documents such as those o the Personnel Classification Board and of other personnel organizations are not complete but these can be supplemented with volumes which are available in the general Pendleton Room Collection"- p. iii of Mr. Baruch's guide.
This collection was originally housed in the Pendleton Room of the U.S. Civil Service Commission, but, was transferred to the Kheel Center in 1997.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Occupations--Classification; Civil service; Personnel management; Baruch, Ismar; United States Civil Service Commission
7053757
- Reports and documents dealing with wages and cost of living, 1836-1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes: Senate report no.355 (24th Congress), House report no.138 (67th Congress) -- Spine title: Documents on Wages and Cost of Living
- Documents dealing with salaries and allowances: the Postal Service, the Foreign Service, the Mechanical Trades: 1914-1930 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  v.1 -- Spine title: Salaries, etc. For Special Groups: 1914-30
- Documents dealing with salaries and allowances: the Customs Service, the Immigration Service: 1927-28, 1922-1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  v.2 -- Spine title: Salaries, etc. For Special Groups: 1927-28
- Documents dealing with salaries and allowances: the Military Services, the Foreign Service, the Customs Service, the Mechanical Trades, the Immigration Service, 1922-1933, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  v.3 -- Spine title: Salaries, etc. For Special Groups: 1922-33
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  v.1. Spine title: Vocational Classification in the Federal Government. Work Papers, J.C.R.S.
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  v.2. Spine title: Classification of Positions in the Federal Government. J.C.R.S.
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  v.3. Spine title: Classification of Positions in the Federal Government. Work Papers, J.C.R.S. McCook Field, Hawaii
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  v.4. Spine title: Vocational Classification in the Federal Government. Work Papers, P.C.B.
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  v.5. Spine title: Vocational Classification in the Federal Government. Work Papers, P.C.B.
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1923-1926 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  v.5A. Spine title: Classification of Positions in the Federal Government. Work Papers, P.C.B.
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1923-1927 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  v.6. Spine title: Classification of Positions in the Federal Government. Work Papers, P.C.B.
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1928-1930 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  v.7. Spine title: Classification of Positions in the Federal Government. Work Papers, P.C.B. Field Survey
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1923-1932 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  v.8. Spine title: Classification of Positions in the Federal Government. Papers, PCB - 1923-32
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1910-1926 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  v.9. Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1910-1926
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1925-1931 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  v.10 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1925-1931
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  v.11 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1931-1932
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1933-1936 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  v.12 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1933-1936
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  v.13 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1937-1939
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1934-1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  v.14 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1934-1942
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1925-1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  v.15 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  v.16A Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1942-1943
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  v.16B Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers, 1942-1943
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1940-1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  v.17 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1941-1944 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  v.18 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  v.19 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  v.20 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  v.21 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers 1943-44
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  v.22 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  v.23 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  v.24 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  v.25 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers 1945-46
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  v.26 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers 1947
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  v.27 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers 1948-50
- Joint Congressional Commission on Reclassification of Salaries: Work papers, 1949-1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  v.28 Spine title: U.S. Classification Papers 1949-52
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 1919-1935 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  v.1 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents and other papers dealing with salary increases and the Classification Act of 1923: 1919-1930 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  v.2 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification, 1919-30
- Classification of Positions in the Federal Government: Official Documents: 1920-24, 1920-1924 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  v.3 Spine title: Classification of Positions in the Federal Government: Official Documents, 1920-24
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  v.4 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: Overtime: 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  v.5 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  v.6 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: S. 807, Federal Employees Pay Act of 1945: Hearings and Reports: April-June, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  v.7 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: Federal Employees Pay Act of 1946: Hearings and Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  v.8 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay, 1943-1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  v.8A Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  v.9 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: Papers dealing with Public Law 900, 80th Congress; S. 1537 and S. 103, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  v.10 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Bills: 1924-1932: In re Classification Board of Civil Service Appeals, consolidation of personnel Activities (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Board of Civil Service Appeals
- Extracts from the Congressional Record: 1921-1923 on the Classification Act of 1923 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Spine title: Congressional Record 1921-1923
- Bills leading up to the Classification Act of 1923: 1921-1923 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Bills preceeding the Classification Act of 1923. Senate 13, Senate 1079, House 8928, 67th Congress: Spine title: Classification Bills 1921-1923
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 81st Congress, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  v.11 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 81st Congress, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  v.12 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 81st Congress, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  v.13 Spine title: Official Documents - Classification
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 81st, 82d and 83d Congress, 1949: (Includes Purvis Committee Reports), 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  v.14 - in binder with 14 on the spine
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 83d Congress, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  v.15 - in binder with 15 on the spine
- Official Documents Classification and Pay: 83d Congress, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  v.16 - in binder with 16 on the spine
- H. R. 15225 in the House of Representatives: December 18, 1920: a Bill to provide for the classification of civilian positions within the District of Columbia and in the field services (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Spine title: H.R. 15225 - 1920
- Classification and Pay Bills: 1931-1937 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  71st, 74th, 75th Congresses. One volume only.
- Official documents dealing with the Welch and Brookhart Acts: 1928-30, 1928-1930 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Spine title: Hearings and Reports, Welch and Brookhart Acts: 1928-30
- Papers in re Amendment of the Classification Act of 1923 by the Welch Act, and the Interpretation of the Latter Act by the Comptroller General: 1928-29, 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Spine title: In re Welch Act
- Bills, 1925-1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Spine title: Miscellaneous Bills
- Overtime Pay Law, 1942: Public Law No. 821, December 22, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Public Law 821. H.R.7144, 77th Congress
- Reports on Classification and Pay Bills., 1935-1937 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Reports on Classification and Pay Bills. General., 1937-1940 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Reports on Classification and Pay Bills. General., 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Reports on Classification and Pay Bills. Special Groups., 1937-1940 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Reports on Classification and Pay Bills. Special Groups., 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Federal Pay Act of 1945 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  v. 1. S.807, 79th Congress
- Wartime health and education, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Wartime health and education hearings, 78th Congress, 2nd Session on S. Res. 74. Spine title: Hearings on Fixed Incomes 1944
- Reports on Pay Legislation., 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  78th and 79th Congresses
- Special Overtime: Inspectional and Investigational Groups, 1944-1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  v. 1. 78th-82nd Congresses; Spine title: Special Overtime Problems
- Special Overtime: Inspectional and Investigational Groups, 1944-1951 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  v. 2. 78th-82nd Congresses; Spine title: Special Overtime Problems
- Special Overtime: Inspectional and Investigational Groups, 1944-1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  v. 3. 78th-82nd Congresses; Spine title: Special Overtime Problems
- Special Overtime: Inspectional and Investigational Groups, 1944-1951 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  v. 4. 78th-82nd Congresses; Spine title: Special Overtime Problems
- Substandard Wages., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Hearings before a subcommittee of the Committee on Education and Labor, U.S. Senate, 2nd Session, Pursuant to S. Con. Res. 48. November 17-18, 1944.
- War Overtime Pay Act of 1943. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  v.1. Public Law 49, 78th Congress
- War Overtime Pay Act of 1943. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  v.2. Public Law 49, 78th Congress
- Federal Employees Pay Act of 1945 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  H.R. 3147, 78th Congress... S.807, 79th Congress
- Federal Employees Pay Act of 1946 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  v. 1. S.1415, 79th Congress
- Federal Employees Pay Act of 1946 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  v. 2. S.1415, 79th Congress
- Federal Pay Act of 1945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  v. 2. S.807, 79th Congress
- Federal Pay Act of 1945 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  v. 3. S.807, 79th Congress
- General Pay Legislation., 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  [v.1]. Legislative Reports, 79th-81st Congresses.
- Legislative Reports: Special Groups., 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  [v.3]. Legislative Reports, 79th-81st Congresses.
- Postal Pay Bills, 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  [v.2]. Legislative Reports, 79th-81st Congresses.
- S.807 Hearings., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  S.807, 79th Congress
- Federal Employees Pay Act of 1946 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  v. 3. S.1415, 79th Congress
- Federal Employees Pay Act of 1946: Bills (Box 10, Folder 2)
  S.1415, 79th Congress
- Federal Employees Salary Act of 1948. Bills. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Public Law 900, S.1537 and H.R.6916, 80th Congress
- Federal Employees Salary Act of 1948. General 1. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Federal Employees Salary Act of 1948. General 2. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Federal Employees Salary Act of 1948. Hearings and Reports. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Public Law 900, S.1537 and H.R.6916, 80th Congress -- Spine title: FESA of 1948 - Hearings and Reports
- Federal Employees Salary Act of 1948. Top 1. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Federal Employees Salary Act of 1948. Top 2. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Reports on Legislation: (General, Special, Top Bracket): 81st Congress, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  81st Congress -- Spine title: Legislative reports - 81st. Cong., Gen.-Sp.-T.B.
- Reports on Pay Legislation (Special Groups, General, and Post Office): 1946, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  79th-80th Congresses -- Spine title: Legislative Reports - Sp. Grps, Gen. & P.O. 1946
- Federal Employees Pay Act of 1946: Hearings and Reports (Box 10, Folder 11)
  S.1415, 79th Congress -- Spine title: S.1415 Hearings and Reports
- Classification Act of 1949, 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  v.1. As amended. 80th-81st Congresses
- Classification Act of 1949, 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  v.2. As amended. 80th-81st Congresses
- Classification Act of 1949, 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  v.3. As amended. 80th-81st Congresses
- Classification Act of 1949. Experimental Schedules, 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  As amended. 80th-81st Congresses
- Classification Act of 1949. Hearings and Reports., 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Classification Act of 1949. Legislative Reports., 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  v.6. 82nd Congresses
- Classification Act of 1949. Operations., 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  v.5. As amended. 80th-81st Congresses. No volume 4.
- Position-Classification and Pay Bills: 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  v.1. 81st Congress -- Spine title: Classification Bills: 1948-1949
- Position-Classification and Pay Bills: 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  v.2. 81st Congress -- Spine title: Classification Bills: 1948-1949
- Classification Act of 1949. Bills., 1948-1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Legislative Reports. Classification Act of 1949., 1948-1952 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  v.1. 81st Congresses -- Spine title: Legislative Reports - 81st Cong.-CA 49 IV
- Material in re history of Federal Classificaiton: 1907-1932 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Includes: Keep Commission report, january 4, 1907; A History of the Government Clerk, by Robert C. Tracy, January 1920; A review of Federal employment classification, by William L. Moore; Other historical surveys, speeches and memos. -- Spine title: Classification History - 1907-32
- Executive Pay Act: Public Law 359, 81st. Congress: 1949 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  v.1. Public Law 359. S.103 and H.R.1689, 81st Congress. -- Spine title: Executive Pay Act, 1949
- Executive Pay Act: Public Law 359, 81st. Congress: 1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  v.2. Public Law 359. S.103 and H.R.1689, 81st Congress. -- Spine title: Executive Pay Act, 1949
- Executive Pay Act of 1949. Bills, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Public Law 359. S.103 and H.R.1689, 81st Congress.
- Executive Pay Act: Public Law 359, 81st. Congress: 1949: Hearings and reports, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Public Law 359. S.103 and H.R.1689, 81st Congress. -- Spine title: Off. Docs. Executive Pay Act, 1948-49
- Quotations in re advantages and purposes of classification, 1902-1923 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  In re classification. -- Spine title: Extracts from reports in re classfication
- Pay Increase Act of 1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Public Law 201. S.622, 82nd Congress.
- Postal Pay Bills: 81st Congress, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  81st Congress. -- Spine title: Reports on Postal Pay Bills, 81st Congress
- Classification and Pay Occupations (Box 13, Folder 1)
  v.1
- Classification and Pay. Special Groups., 1916-1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Classification and Pay. Special Groups., 1916-1945 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  v.2
- Classification and Pay. Special Groups., 1916-1945 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  v.3
- Classification and Pay. Special Groups., 1943-1945 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  [v.4]
- Circulars of the Personnel Classification Board: 1923-1930 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Spine title: P.C.B. Circulars
- Forms of the Personnel Classification Board: 1923-1930 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  v.1 -- Spine title: P.C.B. Forms
- Forms of the Personnel Classification Board: 1923-1930 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  v.2 -- Spine title: P.C.B. Forms
- Questionnaires and Instructions. Classification and Pay., 1919-1945 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  v.1. Federal Agency and other government-jurisdiction forms, questionnaires, surveys. -- Spine title: Questionnaires and instructions
- Questionnaires and Instructions. Classification and Pay., 1919-1945 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  v.2. Federal Agency and other government-jurisdiction forms, questionnaires, surveys. -- Spine title: Questionnaires and instructions
- Classification and Pay. Occupations., 1923-1939 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Papers relating to Field Classification: 1925-1939 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Spine title: Classification. Field Service -- 1925-1939
- Classification. Field Service, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Spine title: Classification. Field Service -- 1935
- General Meaning and Contents of the Professional and Scientific and the Subprofessional Services of the Classification Act, July 25, 1932, by G. Lyle Belsley. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Spine title: The P and SP Services.
- Salaries for Routine Clerical Work in Private Industry. / Personnel Classification Board, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Spine title: Clercal Salaries. PCB.
- Personnel Classification Division. Memos 1-8, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Spine title: Memorandum Nos. 1 to 8 -- 1932
- Salaries and Cost of Living., 1923-1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  v.1. Documents, Clippings, Articles.
- Salaries and Cost of Living., 1923-1951 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  v.2. Documents, Clippings, Articles.
- Salaries and Cost of Living., 1923-1951 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  v.3. Documents, Clippings, Articles.
- Salaries and Cost of Living., 1923-1951 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  v.4. Documents, Clippings, Articles.
- Salaries and Cost of Living., 1923-1951 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  v.5. Documents, Clippings, Articles.
- Federal Salary Classification in Alaska., 1941 (Box 15, Folder 1)